---------------------------------------------------------------------------------
  Changelog for "Rainbeau's Concrete"
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------
- 03/02/2020
	- Updated for RimWorld 1.1

- 12/05/2018
	- Rewrote XML patches to improve load efficiency slightly.

- 12/02/2018
	- Sand piles no longer deteriorate if outside.
	
- 11/04/2018
	- ... And now, pawns will actually *use* the rock mill. (I'd forgotten to add
	  the relevant WorkGiver to the mod yesterday.)
	- Rock mills are now minifiable and movable, and benefit from tool cabinets.
	
- 11/03/2018
	- Added the rock mill (and relevant recipes) from "Fertile Fields" to this
	  mod. This will allow more efficient creation of crushed rocks and sand.
	- It's now possible to create concrete and concrete blocks at a rock mill,
	  faster and more efficiently than at a stonecutting table.
	- Added patches so that glass from "Glass+Lights" and "Dub's Skylights"
	  is actually made from sand.
	- Fixed the concrete and cement graphics so they have black borders like
	  all other items.

- 10/29/2018
	- Embrasures now have slightly higher resource costs than do normal walls.
	- The market value of concrete "cinder" blocks has been cut roughly in half,
	  to the value of regular stone blocks.
	- The market value of concrete has been cut to 2.5, a third of its previous
	  value.
	  
- 10/24/2018
	- Fixed a minor problem with drops from deconstructed deep bridges, which had
	  snuck into the mod in the upgrade from b19 to 1.0.
	- Clarified in the descriptions of embrasures that they act essentially as
	  permanently-open vents, equalizing temperatures on both sides of a wall.
	  
- 10/14/2018
	- Updated to RimWorld 1.0 release!
	- Updated some of the mod's graphics (primarily to utilize StackCounts).

- 10/09/2018
	- Updated to RimWorld b19 release.
	- It's now possible to build doors, vents, etc., directly on the mod's walls,
	  just as on vanilla walls.
	- Added a single-step "stone chunks + cement = concrete" recipe.
	- Updated the version of the Harmony library the mod uses.
	- Removed "Mod Sync Ninja" files.

- 01/20/2018
	- Made a few changes (to recipe work times, resource values, and crushed
	  rock stack size) to match recent changes in "Fertile Fields."
	- Cut the work times for mod-specific recipes in half, to balance with the
	  other recipe work time changes.

- 12/04/2017
	- The mod now works with the "Mod Sync Ninja" updater.

- 11/24/2017
	- This mod can now be used independently of "Fertile Fields," though I still
	  suggest that they be used together, as without "Fertile Fields," options
	  for obtaining crushed rocks and sand are a bit limited.

- 11/19/2017
	- Updated to RimWorld b18 release.

- 9/24/2017
	- Reinforced concrete has been renamed "steel-reinforced concrete," and
	  plasticrete is now "plasteel-reinforced concrete."
	- Steel-reinforced walls now require "Machining" to have been researched.
	  (I realize there's no direct correlation between machining and bunker wall
	  construction, but I didn't want to add a brand-new tech just for this, and
	  machining seems to represent about the right technological competence and
	  conceptual research focus, and it's something that nobody starts the game
	  with.) Plasteel-reinforced walls additionally require "Microelectronics
	  Basics" research.

- 08/06/2017
	- Plasticrete doors now have the durability they should have had already.

- 08/05/2017
	- Costs for concrete and concrete walls, and strengths of concrete walls,
	  have been rebalanced to bring them more into line with vanilla materials.
	  Cinder block walls are now much cheaper to build, and are actually a viable
	  option for quick wall production. Poured concrete walls are now comparable
	  in strength to granite walls, but easier to build in bulk. And reinforced
	  concrete walls are no longer absurdly overpowered, but rather are just shy
	  of plasteel walls in strength. Thanks to Ludeon forum user KitsuneKas for
	  doing all the math and suggesting how things ought to be adjusted.
	- To appease those who liked the absurdly overpowered walls, one final wall
	  option has been added. Reinforced plasticrete walls are massive defensive
	  fortifications constructed from layers of concrete, steel, plasteel and,
	  according to some, the blood of sacrificial virgins.
	- Deep water bridges from "Basic Bridges" now correctly leave crushed rocks
	  instead of bags of concrete when deconstructed or destroyed.

- 07/23/2017
	- Reinforced concrete autodoors now open just slightly slower than stone
	  block autodoors, instead of opening just as fast as plasteel autodoors.

- 07/23/2017
	- Added reinforced concrete doors to match the reinforced concrete walls.
	- Concrete walls, doors and floors return crushed rocks when deconstructed.
	- Added embrasures that can be built from vanilla wall materials and from
	  clay bricks.
	- Moved embrasures from the Structure tab of the Architect menu to the	
	  Security tab.

- 06/18/2017
	- Cement and concrete are somewhat more likely to be found on bulk traders,
	  as per changes in "Fertile Fields."
	- Limestone blocks, as well as limestone chunks, can now be used in the 
	  creation of cement.
	- Cement recipes default to allowing only limestone, but can be adjusted to
	  accept other stone types, as well.

- 06/14/2017
	- Added cement, which is made in a smithy from limestone chunks.
	- Making concrete no longer requires steel, but instead requires cement.
	- Concrete is now made at a stonecutting table instead of at a rock mill. I
	  wanted to make sure that concrete production didn't require electricity,
	  since historically it's been used since ancient times.
	- Cinder block walls are now weaker than granite walls, and aren't pretty.
	  But they can be built quickly.
	- Reinforced concrete walls are now much stronger than they were originally.
	- A new wall type, "poured concrete wall," splits the difference.

- 06/12/2017
	- Initial release.
